When a man is healed, that person has
power to begin to move. But when a
family is healed, a society has power to
begin to move. The foundation of
communities and societies is family.
When you want to kill a nation, don't
attack the president. Attack the family
unit. Because once the family unit is
destroyed, you have no nation. Because
it is families that come together that
form a community and communities that
come together form a society and
societies that come together form a
nation. So this when families come
together they form a a community and
when communities come together they form
a society. When societies come together
they form a nation and when nations come
together they form a continent. So if
you want to attack a nation, begin by
attacking the tenants, the fabric and
the values of the family. And we live in
a time where this attack is not private.
We live in a time where men are
celebrating divorce. We live in a time
whereby having baby mas is and having a
candle is the order of the day. But we
cannot be quiet when we know the truth.
WHEN A CAR VEERS OFF FROM THE ROAD, you
don't continue with the journey out of
the main road. You take it back to the
original road. And so we must take the
car back to the original road. And this
month we are going to be very real. I
spoke to one of my friends uh who
divorced and I told him sir come and
talk to us because there are young
people here who are saying
and I said I want you to come and open
up and share and tell us were there
things that you think you'd have done
better so that those who are on the exit
door there are people who are married
but
they have already packed in their minds
and I believe that there will be healing
and restoration of marriages
Hallelujah. But this morning, allow me
to talk about altars versus versus the
altar.
Altars versus the altar.
Now, I've written a book and I've
addressed the four battles of families.
I I they there are many. In fact, I've
addressed five of them, but in details,
I have addressed the four. And number
one, I have addressed the issue of
generational cases. These are battles
that are in families, generational
curses. A curse is an utterance released
by an authority wishing you doom. A
curse is an utterance. It's a word, an
utterance released by an authority, a
person in power. A curse is an utterance
released by an authority wishing you
doom or chaos. This is someone who sees
a father, a mother, a grandfather,
grandmother, an authority in a family
and they wish you doom. That's a curse.
And the problem with a curse is that it
can affect you and generations to come.
Because when I suffer, even my daughter
will suffer automatically. Whatever I go
through, if my businesses, my life, my
career does not pick up, it
automatically tells me there will be an
extrapolation to the next generation.
So, and we are not here yet to look upon
curses. Then there is a generational
pattern. A generational pattern. These
are sequences
that are that are that are that are in
our lives. These are these are sequences
that can be observed. observable
sequences in our lives.
observable sequences in our lives and
and this is very common because even in
the medical science there's something
they ask whether you have generational
diseases that begins to tell you there
are things that are transferable through
the element of the DNA
that the fact that YOU BELONG TO A
CERTAIN family there are things that can
be transferred through the DNA one of
the common diseases is diabetes
you You you are just born in a home
where diabetes rules and you are told by
the doctors you are a good candidate OF
DIABETES. WHY? NOT BECAUSE YOU HAVE a
wrong lifestyle but because it is
transferable through the DNA and even
spiritually there are things that can be
transferred generationally.
THERE ARE HABITS AND CHARACTERS THAT CAN
BE TRANSFERRED even as far as that
generation. I I met someone who was
named after their grandmother and they
behave like that grandmother. So So
there are things when we come we begin
TO SEE NAMES THERE are names that carry
ordinations that people given a certain
name bear a certain feature because they
are ordinances upon names. Uh we also
find um a certain pattern and some of
these patterns are initiated by a
person. It just takes one man to be
careless and divorce and open up a door
of divorce. So if today I divorce my
wife, my children, IF THEY DON'T STAND
on salvation and if they don't know
Jesus and get to know the reality of
their redemption, they might suffer the
consequences of my action because I've
opened a door and I've introduced a
pattern in my bloodline. SO MY DAUGHTER
MIGHT GET MARRIED AND DIVORCE NOT
BECAUSE SHE really wants but there is
such a claim there is a pattern that she
was born under. Are you hearing me? And
that's why THERE IS A PLACE IN LIFE
WHERE WE MUST FORGET ourselves and fight
for the sake of generations to come.
There is A PLACE WE HOLD ON NOT BECAUSE
THINGS are okay but because the next
generation is waiting on our victory and
they can build upon OUR VICTORY. THAT'S
WHY WE CAN'T JUST be in issues and say
be you know whatever I feel I will do
it. There is a time when God looks at
you as a savior. In the book of 1 John
3:16, THE BIBLE SAYS, "NOW LAY YOUR
LIFE." Jesus laid his life in John 3:16.
BUT IN 1 JOHN 3:16, THE BIBLE NOW CALLS
US TO LAY OUR LIVES TO LAY OUR LIVES now
as as a sacrifice. There is a place
where you can die
um in his life. AND WE ALSO OUGHT TO LAY
DOWN OUR LIVES FOR THE BRETHREN. Jesus
laid his life AND HE'S ALSO CALLING US
ONCE in a while to lay our lives. Are we
together? So there's a place where you
can also purpose AND SAY MAY I be the
one to stand ON THIS GATE, FIGHT AND
change the course and the navigation of
my generation. So we have these
patterns.
Number three, we have generational
iniquity. Whatever they call the
mistakes of the fathers.
The mistakes of the fathers. this
iniquity. Iniquity is something you do
that attracts judgment.
There is transgression.
There is trespass. There is iniquity.
ALL THESE ARE UNDER the definition of
sin.
Sin is missing the mark.
But when we BEGIN TO DEFINE ELEMENTS OF
SIN TO TRESPASS SIMPLY MEANS THERE IS an
order a good example that I can give is
THERE IS AN INSTRUCTION ON THE wall
and that's exactly where you go now that
point has gone home. AMEN. NOW WHAT ARE
you doing? YOU ARE YOU are trespassing.
Are you getting it? THERE THERE YOU ARE
TRESPASSING. THEN THERE IS
TRANSGRESSION.
Violation of a law. You know that THIS
IS WRONG BUT YOU STILL VIOLATE IT. You
know that you know you have not left
your house but you are the one saying
Buddhi.
You know and you KNOW IT WILL TAKE YOU
30 MINUTES and you say 5 minutes I'll be
there. Transgression. And then there is
iniquity. When you do something without
remorse. You know it is wrong but you do
it and you don't care and you don't
repent and judgment is attracted.
And so iniquity attracts judgment. AND
SOMETIMES WHEN JUDGMENT IS PASSED THAT
JUDGMENT NOT ONLY AFFECTS THE PERSON but
affects generations.
We see this pattern in the Bible. The
children of Eli mess up with the
offerings of the Lord. AND THE LORD
JUDGES THE HOUSE OF Eli and says in this
house IN THIS HOUSE NO SON SHALL GROW
above the FLOWERY AGE. MEANING THAT
people died as teenagers BECAUSE THEY
ARE FATHERS MESSED UP. SO YOU ARE BORN
IN THAT HOME YOU HAVE YOUR VISION BUT
THERE IS A RULING THERE IS A VERDICT.
YOU CAN'T grow of a certain age
and then there are generational altars.
And the way you are looking at me, I can
tell most of you these matters are
green.
And I think we'll handle them.
I don't want to assume that those who
are here last year are the ones who are
here this year. Is that okay? Yes. So we
will handle them and I'll encourage you.
The book has everything. In fact, this
what I will do. We will reprint the book
and then give you the book and tell you
go and read it for one month. And then
after one month we come and do a series
because now I've I've read I've done a
research I've written a book. Now what
else? Yes.
because these are things THAT ARE GOING
NOT just to help you but even
generations to come you will understand
some of THESE THINGS. NOW TODAY I WANT
TO DEAL WITH altars generational altars
and uh and this is a conversation
that
I know it has been taught
BUT IF WE DON'T BALANCE OUR THEOLOGY WE
ARE GOING to sell deception.
There are messages as a preacher I'll
tell you there are sermons IF YOU ARE
NOT SENSITIVE TO SHARE THE whole council
it is very possible to teach it halfway
and introduce errors
and this is one of them this is one of
the teachings that HAS ATTRACTED A LOT
OF manipulation
and for me just to say directly it has
attracted a lot of witchcraft craft on
the altars of God. Now, let's look at it
basic. What is an altar?
An altar?
An altar
is an erected monument,
a raised or an erected monument.
An altar is an erected monument
THAT ACTS AS A GATE of transaction.
that acts as a gate of transaction
between the spiritual realm and the
physical realm. An altar is an erected
monument
THAT ACTS as a gate of transaction
between the spiritual realm and the
physical realm.
That tells you it takes a man to raise
an altar. Altars don't raise themselves.
THAT IS WHY IT'S an erected monument.
And it acts as a gate between this
physical realm and the real of the
spirit. SO A MAN IS IN CHARGE OF RAISING
AN ALTAR. AND THAT ALTAR ACTS AS A GATE,
AS an opening, as an entry point
of transactions between the spiritual
realm and the physical. SO THERE ARE
THINGS THAT happen here THAT BEGIN TO
AFFECT THAT REALM and that real begins
to affect this realm.
The second definition of an altar. An
altar is an elevated base.
An altar is an elevated base
for spiritual or religious sacrifices.
An altar is an elevated base. Is
something that is raised for spiritual
or religious sacrifices. That's an
altar. An elevated base.
AN ALTAR WITHOUT A SACRIFICE IS a
monument.
AN ALTAR WITHOUT A SACRIFICE IS AN
MONUMENT.
WHATEVER GIVES STRENGTH TO ALTARS IS
SACRIFICE.
AND THE FREQUENCY OF sacrifice is what
strengthens an altar.
IT IS THE FREQUENCY OF SACRIFICE THAT
GIVES strength to an altar.
It is possible to sacrifice without
altars. BUT YOU CAN NEVER HAVE ALTARS
WITHOUT SACRIFICES.
Am I going too far?
I've said AN ALTAR WITHOUT A SACRIFICE
is a monument. That's just an image.
And the frequency of sacrifice, THE MORE
YOU SACRIFICE ON THAT ALTAR, the
stronger it becomes.
And it IS POSSIBLE FOR MEN TO sacrifice
without altars. But it is impossible for
an altar to survive without a sacrifice.
THE FIRST SACRIFICE IN THE Bible was
given without an altar.
IT WAS GIVEN BY ABEL. ABEL gave the
first sacrifice. THERE WAS NO ALTAR.
They were just worshiping the Lord. AND
THEY BROUGHT THEIR SACRIFICES THERE. THE
THERE some version called them
offerings. Cain brought his and Abel
BROUGHT HIS. AND THERE WAS A REACTION
FROM THE HEAVENS. THE LORD HONORED ABEL
AND honored his sacrifice.
SO IT IS POSSIBLE. THAT'S WHY THERE ARE
MEN THAT SACRIFICE UNDER TREES AND
there's no altar. Are you getting me?
THERE ARE PEOPLE THAT sacrifice in the
sea and there is no altar. They just
slaughter and release sacrifices.
THE FIRST ALTAR TO BE RAISED IN THE
BIBLE was raised by Noah.
NOAH IS THE FATHER THAT PIONEERED THE
SYSTEM OF ALTARS.
AND HE RAISED AN ALTAR AFTER THE FLOODS.
AND THAT ALTAR
changed the mind of God WHEN HE RAISED
THAT ALTAR AND BURNT A SACRIFICE. WE
SAID AN altar without a sacrifice is A
MONUMENT. WHEN THAT ALTAR BURNT A
SACRIFICE, THE LORD SMELT FROM HEAVEN.
AND HE SAID, "FROM NOW, I WILL NEVER
PUNISH MAN."
WHY? BECAUSE WHEN ADAM FELL, THERE WAS A
SEPARATION BETWEEN MAN AND GOD.
BUT A MAN PIONEERED A SYSTEM OF DEALING
WITH A SPIRITUAL GOD BY THE
FUNCTIONARIES OF AN ALTAR.
THE ONE WHO GAVE HIM THE INTELLIGENCE OF
ALTARS. NO ONE KNOWS BUT SOME THINGS are
revealed. Hallelujah. AND AND AND THIS
IS NOW WHEN GOD LOOKED UPON MAN AND SAID
NEVER AGAIN SHALL I DESTROY THE WHOLE
WORLD BECAUSE THE FUNCTION OF MAN HAS
BEEN RESTORED A WORSHSHIPER. So this man
raised an altar
and a SACRIFICE TO CONNECT WITH GOD. Now
this is Old Testament.
When we go further in the Old Testament,
WE BEGIN TO SEE THERE WERE ALSO ALTARS
THAT WERE RAISED. Look at Exodus 34:13.
Exodus 34:13.
But you SHALL DESTROY MAYBE LUKE 12.
Take heed to yourself, lest you make a
covenant with the inhabitants OF THE
LAND WHERE YOU ARE GOING, lest it be a
snare in your midst. Now, this is God
talking to Israel and saying, as you
enter that land, what is THAT LAND?
CANAAN, AS YOU enter that land, don't
make covenants with those people. AND
THEN NOW HE GOES TO 13 AND GIVES THEM A
VERY POWERFUL INSTRUCTION.
But you shall destroy THEIR ALTARS,
BREAK their sacred pillars, AND CUT DOWN
their wooden images. Look at 14. FOR YOU
SHALL WORSHIP NO OTHER GOD. FOR THE LORD
WHOSE NAME IS JEALOUS IS A JEALOUSY GOD.
NOW YOU CAN NEVER FIND AN ALTAR WITHOUT
A GOD. Altars are erected to gods EITHER
GO D CAPITAL OR GO d small. THAT IS WHY
YOU NEVER FIND ALTARS WITHOUT GODS. WHEN
WE TALK ABOUT GENERATIONAL ALTARS, WE
MUST ALSO ASK OURSELVES, WHAT WERE THE
GENERATIONAL GODS?
I want to BELIEVE PASTOR PETER SPOKE
ABOUT HOUSEHOLD GODS.
Household gods. It's there in the Bible.
Let's look at Genesis
31:19.
Household gods. Genesis 31:19
NOW LABAN HAD GONE TO SHEER HIS SHEEP
AND RTO HAD STOLEN THE HOUSEHOLD IDOLS
THAT WERE HER FATHERS.
So we begin TO SEE THAT ANYWHERE YOU
HAVE A GENERATIONAL ALTAR, THERE MUST BE
a generational God.
LOOK AT JUDGES CHAPTER 6 26 and 27.
Judges 6:26 and 27
maybe beginning from 25.
Now it came to pass the same night that
the Lord said TO HIM, "TAKE YOUR
FATHER'S YOUNG BULL, THE SECOND bull of
7 years old, AND TEAR DOWN THE ALTAR OF
BAL THAT YOUR FATHER HAS, AND CUT DOWN
THE WOODEN IMAGE that is BESIDE IT."
LOOK, THERE WAS AN ALTAR OF BAL AND
there was an image of a god
because altars are BASES WHERE
SACRIFICES ARE RAISED to deities
alone.
SO ANYTIME YOU FIND AN ALTAR, YOU MUST
INTERROGATE THE GODS being woripped.
AND THE BIBLE SAYS WHEN YOU ENTER
CANAAN, BRING DOWN THE ALTARS OF BAL AND
DESTROY THE HIGH PLACES BECAUSE ALTARS
ARE BASIS OF sacrifices
for gods.
So we will come to Gideon's story
because this is a very common story. We
see that Gideon located the altar and
the god in his father's house and Gideon
BROUGHT DOWN THE ALTAR AND THE GOD and
now HE NEVER LEFT IT AT THAT BECAUSE THE
REALM OF THE SPIRIT DOES NOT ACCOMMODATE
VACUUMS
IN YOUR LIFE.
THERE MUST BE an altar speaking EITHER
THE ALTAR OF YAHWEH OR ANOTHER ALTAR.
BUT THE REAL OF the spirit is never
quite.
Now look at what happened after he
pulled down and build an ALTAR TO THE
LORD GOD ON TOP OF THIS ROCK IN THE
PROPER ARRANGEMENT AND TAKE THE SECOND
BULL AND OFFER BURNT OFFERING. WHAT DID
HE DO? HE CLEARED THE ALTARS IN HIS
FATHER'S HOUSE AND RAISED THE altar of
the Lord in the same house.
I want us to begin to study the pattern.
NUMBER ONE, WE BEGIN TO SEE that every
ALTAR RAISED IN THE OLD Testament was
unto the Lord. So they took away the
altars that were not of God and
introduced the altar of God.
Are we together? Because nature does not
permit what? Vacuum. So meaning THAT
WHEN YOU BRING DOWN, YOU MUST BRING UP.
THAT WAS THE ANOINTING UPON JEREMIAH. GO
AND bring down. BUT ABOVE ALL, BUILD UP.
YOU DON'T LEAVE A VACUUM. YOU MUST BRING
DOWN AND BUILD UP. BECAUSE IF A VACUUM
IS LEFT, THAT altar will begin to
operate.
NOW THIS IS THE PATTERN OF THE OLD
TESTAMENT. REMEMBER MAJORITY OF THE
STUFF IN THE OLD Testament existed as
images
and shadows.
AND THAT IS WHY MEN COULD RAISE ALTARS.
But even THE ALTARS THEY RAISED, IT WAS
NOT OUT OF THEIR OWN.
THERE WAS A PATTERN ON HOW TO RAISE THAT
ALTAR.
YOU DIDN'T JUST WAKE UP AND SAY, "I FEEL
LIKE RAISING AN ALTAR." AND then you
raise and then say, "I feel LIKE THIS
ALTAR, WE NEED TO SACRIFICE SEVEN
BULLS." AND then you sacrifice. No,
there was a pattern. There were
instructions.
The first pattern was that a a a Jewish
altar needed 12 stones and cut
12 that have not faced any chisel.
That's the first thing. The second
thing, it needed A CLEAN ANIMAL. YOU
COULDN'T JUST SACRIFICE ANYTHING ON that
altar. You needed to go to the Levitical
law and look AT ANIMALS THAT WERE SET
APART AND CONSIDERED TO BE CLEAN AND YOU
SACRIFICE IT THERE. THE BAD THING, NOT
EVERY MAN HAD THE POWER OF RAISING
ALTARS.
THIS MATTER OF ALTARS WAS ENTRUSTED to
the Levitical priesthood. SO NOT EVERY
MAN COULD WAKE UP AND RAISE AN ALTAR.
THE PRIESTLYHOOD WAS THE ONE MANDATED
WITH the assignment of governing altars.
THE ONLY THING THAT MEN BROUGHT WAS THE
SACRIFICE.
AND ANYONE THAT RAISED AN ALTAR WAS
instructed by God. Like this ONE IS TOLD
GO AND TAKE THE BULL seven years. That's
an instruction. SEVEN IS VERY PROPHETIC.
I AM ONE FROM YOUR FATHER. THEN RAISE AN
ALTAR. THE LORD GIVES INSTRUCTIONS ON
HOW THAT ALTAR OUGHT TO BE BECAUSE THERE
IS AN ASIAN PATTERN ON ALTARS THAT
ATTRACTED THE ATTENTION of Zion.
NOT EVERY ALTAR RAISED BY A MAN
ATTRACTED his attention. THERE WAS A
PATTERN ON HOW IT OUGHT TO BE DONE. AND
THERE WAS AN AUTHORITY THAT GOD GAVE MAN
SO THAT MAN CAN RAISE AN ALTAR FOR GOD
BECAUSE MAN HAS NO POWER AND CAPACITY TO
RAISE AN altar for God.
Unless God INSTRUCTS YOU, THE DEMANDS OF
GOD ARE SO HIGH THAT UNLESS HE TELLS YOU
HOW WHATEVER YOU ARE doing does not
match. Can we are we getting this
matters? Yes, we have no capacity
UNLESS
three then at that
BECAUSE THE THE REASON WHY SACRIFICES
WERE PLACED ON ALTARS IS SO THAT MEN CAN
GET THE ATTENTION OF GODS.
THE HIGH PLACES OF BAL THERE WAS A
PATTERN. THEY HAD THE PRIESTS OF BAL
THAT GOVERNED AND MANAGED THE ACTIVITIES
OF the high place.
So not just ANYONE
IN OUR FAMILIES.
HOW DO MEN OPEN GATES through altars?
Number one, witchcraft.
Witchcraft. There are four There are
four gates that can be opened in a
family.
Number one, witchcraft.
Number two, Freemasonry.
Freemasonry. DON'T BE DECEIVED THAT ALL
FREEMASONS DON'T DO RITUALS. ALL
FREEMASONS ARE there to help the
community. Don't be deceived. If your
work is to help the community, your
matters will be public. Why is it a
secret society? How do you ascend in
ranks? They are rituals.
Number three, Satanism.
And number four, occultism,
witchcraft, freemasonry, satanism, and
occultism. And I'm going to explain
them. Let's begin with witchcraft.
What is witchcraft?
How do witchcraft operate?
HAVE YOU REALIZED THE FIRST ALTAR WAS
RAISED BY A MAN WITHOUT any manual? It
took intelligence of the spirit to tell
Noah raise an altar. Even on this other
kingdom
WHO WHO TAUGHT OUR GRANDFATHERS THAT
WHEN YOU DO ONE TWO three spirits will
respond. These are matters. YOU DON'T
NEED A UNIVERSITY to be taught about
altars.
that spirits can teach you on how to
invoke them and influence them.
AND SO WITCHCRAFT, THIS IS VERY COMMON
IN OUR FAMILIES AND COMMUNITIES. PEOPLE
WANT TO BRAND IT AND CALL IT OUR
TRADITIONAL WAYS OF LIFE. PEOPLE WANT TO
BRAND IT AND SAY, YOU KNOW, WHEN THE
WHITE PEOPLE CAME, THEY CAME AND SAY
THAT THIS IS WRONG AND AND THEIR STUFF
IS RIGHT. THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
white people. LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, THE
REAL OF THE SPIRIT IS NOT RACIST.
THAT REAL DOES NOT ANSWER TO COLOR. IT
ANSWERS TO PROTOCOL. THAT A WHITE MAN
CAN RAISE AN ALTAR IN THE PATTERNS OF
BLACK MAGIC IN NIGERIA AND DEMONS will
answer. SO THIS IS NOT A RACE QUESTION.
A CHINESE CAN INVOKE VOODOO WHICH WAS
PIONEERED in Nigeria and it will work.
SO THIS IS A LANGUAGE OF BEING TAUGHT
how to SUMMON DEMONS. THE SPIRIT BEHIND
WITCHCRAFT IS MANIPULATION. THAT IS THE
CORE BUSINESS. AND you you you SOMETIMES
YOU HAVE MINOR WITCHES. They are not yet
senior.
People who begin to tell you if you love
me WE NEED TO HAVE SEX for you to prove
that YOU LOVE ME. YOU ARE A WITCH.
YOU BEGAN YOU YOU'RE ON THE PATHWAY OF
witchcraft
because it is manipulation.
DON'T WAIT FOR A MAN WITH A A ROUND EYE
AND A MASAI GARMENT. NO, YOU IN A SUIT.
You keep on as A MESSY. NO, YOU ARE a
witch in a suit.
Because you are there to control and
manipulate.
Hallelujah. And that's why NOW BY BY BY
THIS CONCEPT OF CONTROL AND
MANIPULATION, THEY NOW WANT TO PARTNER
WITH DEMONS.
SO THAT WHATEVER YOU DO IS NOT OUT OF
your consent.
ANOTHER POWER IS IN CONTROL OF YOUR
LIFE, YOUR SENSES, YOUR OPERATIONS, YOUR
DEALINGS. SO NOW THEY HAVE TO INVOKE
ANOTHER POWER. AND THE ONLY WAY TO
ACCESS THE REALM OF THE SPIRIT is by an
altar. SO A WITCH WHERE WITCHES ARE
WHATEVER THEY SERVICE IS AN ALTAR. AND
THAT IS why every witch will make a
demand of a sacrifice.
But they will NEVER ASK FOR A SACRIFICE
UNTIL THEY know what you want.
You will GO AND THEY WILL ASK YOU SO
WHAT IS THE PROBLEM? And you say I want
to get married by who? By this man.
Uhhuh. No, I just want him to love me
and as he comes to church, I don't want
him to see ANY GIRL. OKAY. NOW, THEY
already know there is a demon I need to
SUMMON BECAUSE THE DEMANDS YOU HAVE
PLACED CAN ONLY BE MET BY A CERTAIN
DEMON. AND THAT DEMON CAN BE summoned by
a certain sacrifice. So that's now
that's when they WILL TELL YOU GO AND DO
ONE 2 THREE. WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW? NOW
YOU ARE INTRODUCING A SACRIFICE ON THAT
ALTAR. NOW THAT ALTAR BEARS YOUR NAME.
SO NATURALLY YOU HAVE OPENED A DOOR OF
TRANSACTION.
Now demons don't die but men die. Now
I'm a father in my family and I'm hungry
for wealth and I don't care how I'll get
wealthy. And I SEE A POSTER WRITTEN
Tanzania and I take the NUMBER AND I GO
SOMEWHERE in I meet them Ganga and he
tells me now listen sir this is what you
need to do the first thing WE WILL GIVE
YOU POWER but in this power you need to
buy 20 goats black in color and as you
bring them this is 50,000 the next thing
you need to do you need to GET THIS
STUFF AND GO AND DO ONE TO THREE SO I GO
AND FULFILL ALL THE DEMANDS OF THAT
ALTAR AND SLOWLY I AM GROWING BUT MY
BACKING IS DEMONIC. So demons begin to
give me demonic backup and my businesses
PROSPER AND MY CHILDREN ARE NOW IN
NATIONAL SCHOOLS. I AM I AM DRIVING THE
LATEST. I AM LIVING IN the best OF
ESTATE. BUT EVERY TIME THERE IS A DEMAND
ON THIS ALTAR, I MUST GO AND SERVICE THE
ALTAR. So every year because I need more
power, I need to give MORE SACRIFICE SO
THAT THESE demons keep on giving me
backup. NOW THE DAY I DIE, MY CHILDREN
WILL BE UNDER THE DEMONS THAT I OPEN A
DOOR. WHETHER THEY KNOW IT OR NOT, THEY
will suffer BECAUSE DEMONS DON'T DIE.
BUT THE MAN WHO OPENED THAT DOOR HAS
DIED. AND THEY ARE THERE LEGALLY BECAUSE
I'M THE ONE WHO GAVE A SACRIFICE. THEY
WERE SUMMONED TO HELP ME. SO THEIR
OPPRESSION IS LEGALLY. SO IF THAT ALTAR
IS NOT SERVICED AND THE DEMANDS OF THAT
ALTARS ARE NOT MET, THEN THE DEMONS
BEGIN TO REACT and poverty hits that
house and all THE THINGS I GATHER
DEMONICALLY begins to disappear because
there was a demonic backup for me to be
where I am. SO SUDDENLY MY BUSINESSES
COLLAPSE. SUDDENLY MY CHILDREN ARE NOW
SUFFERING POVERTY AND WHATEVER THEY DO
CAN NEVER PROSPER because I opened a
door.
AND THAT IS WHERE GOD COMES IN BECAUSE
HE SAYS UPON THIS ROCK I'LL BUILD MY
CHURCH AND THE GATES OF HELL CANNOT
PREVAIL AND I'VE given you the KEYS OF
THE KINGDOM. WHATEVER YOU OPEN IS OPEN
AND WHATEVER YOU BIND IS BOUND. AND
PLEASE LET ME SAY THIS VERY CLEARLY.
THERE IS A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN MEN THAT
ARE tied to demonic ALTARS AND MEN THAT
ARE LAZY AND THEY'RE LOOKING FOR
EXCUSES.
SOME OF YOU, THERE IS NO ALTAR HARASSING
YOUR LIFE. YOU ARE LAZY AND POOR OUT OF
LAZINESS. PERIOD. SO PLEASE DON'T GO
INTERROGATING WAS MY GRANDFATHER A
WITCH? WAS MY UNCLE A WITCH? AND THEN
YOU SAY IT LOOKS like the SISTER OF MY
GRANDFATHER WAS A WITCH AND I THINK
THAT'S WHERE THE PROBLEM IS. NO, PLEASE
YOU ARE LAZY. PLEASE WAKE UP, WORK HARD,
STOP USING THIS GOSPEL as a scapegoat.
The Bible says a little slumber, A
LITTLE FOLDING AND POVERTY COMES
KNOCKING. THAT'S WHERE YOU ARE SLUMBER.
And many people are now using this as a
scape goat. Pastor,
THERE'S A MAN WHO CAME TO THE office
for counseling. Met one of the PASTORS
AND SAID,
AND THE PASTOR ASKED HIM, "OKAY, let me
see the termination letter." The guy had
not gone to jail for almost one week. He
had not told anyone he's not coming. And
the pastor said,
"SO SUCH A PERSON DOES NOT HAVE ANY
DEVIL. ARE YOU GETTING ME? SOME OF YOU
ARE JUST LAZY. SO please stop USING THIS
MESSAGE AND SAYING
NO. LIFE WE NEED PATIENCE. WE DON'T WAKE
UP AND BECOME SUCCESSFUL." YOU NEED TO
UNDERSTAND THE POWER OF WORKING HARD,
THE POWER OF BUILDING SLOWLY. YOU NEED
TO UNDERSTAND THAT WE HAVE NO LESSONS IN
SUCCESS. OUR LESSONS ARE IN FAILURE.
There's no lesson in success. IT IS WHEN
WE FAIL, we learn. AND IT DOESN'T MEAN
WHEN WE FAIL THAT GOD IS NOT WITH US.
NO. When I was in Mombasa, the Lord was
telling me there is something I train my
children is called the power of
endurance. Asked him, "What do you
mean?" He said when you go to the
military they always take you through a
session and they tell you in this
session for the next one week you'll
sleep for three to three for two to
three hours and they'll ask you do you
think you can make it and many people
always feel up and say I don't think I
must sleep 6 hours it is healthy and
then they take you through a training
where you sleep for two hours for almost
a week and after one week they ask you
how was it and they say I didn't know I
could face it the lord TOLD ME GO AND
ASK MY CHILDREN HOW MANY OF THEM HAVE A
testimony of saying how I came out. I
don't know. I WAS TRYING TO INTRODUCE TO
THEM WHAT THEY ARE MADE OF. THAT'S WHY I
NEVER TAMPED OUT WITH THAT PROCESS. I
WANTED THEM TO KNOW AND THAT'S WHY WHEN
MEN ARE CIRCUMCISED IN THAT LEVEL, THEY
CAN risk in any matter. People that have
made losses, they are RISK TAKERS. SOME
OF US ARE TOO SAFE for life. When you go
to the swimming pool, THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO TEST THE WATER, THEN THEY STAY
ASIDE. BUT THERE ARE MEN WHO HAVE BEEN
SWIMMING, THEY GO TO THE DEEP END AND
JUMP. WHY? THEY HAVE BEEN THERE BEFORE.
IF YOU'VE not been there, you put your
water, then you stay, then you put your
hand, THEN YOU STAY. NO, THAT'S NOT HOW
YOU APPROACH LIFE.
And that's why THERE ARE SEASONS YOU GO
IN LIFE AND GOD IS QUIET. He's saying,
"Sir, I want to reveal to you what you
are made of. YOU'LL NEVER KNOW THAT YOU
CANNOT DIE OUT OF A HEARTBREAK." NOW,
I'M ABOUT TO tell you, you cannot die.
You will cry FOR TWO WEEKS, BUT
HEARTBREAK CAN NEVER KILL YOU. THEN NEXT
TIME YOU GO ON FACEBOOK AND SAY,
"WHATEVER DOES NOT KILL YOU MAKES YOU
STRONGER." AND THE LORD SAYS, "YES, it
is true."
Hallelujah.
SO, SO I'M TRYING TO RAISE THIS SO THAT
WE HAVE A BALANCE. Are we together? Some
people don't have a which they don't
have a problem with witchcraft. They
just have a problem with laziness, lack
of strategy, lack of empowerment, lack
of reading books. They are prayer
warriors, but they are warriors on the
world. They worry a lot, but they pray a
lot. So we just need to have forums,
teach you on business, teach you on
manners OF SAVING. YOU CANNOT survive on
feliza the whole of the year. If you're
not saving, you're a fool.
>> Yes. You can't EAT BREAD AND AND SIN AT
THE SAME TIME. SO YOU JUST NEED
EMPOWERMENT FORUMS. HALLELUJAH.
>> YES. And then there are some of us FOR
REAL THERE'S SOMETHING AFFECTING them
and now we need to tell them how to GET
OUT SO THAT AGAIN THEY DON'T GET
comfortable being stagnating in one
level and lifting the devil and making
it look like you know this is where I
am. So the first door is witchcraft.
HAVE YOU SEEN HOW witchcraft operates? A
door is open and the spirits are there
legally. And so the there is a way how
we can deal with them and kick them out.
Uh we we are also here legally. So we
are not HERE ILLEGALLY. IN FACT, THE
SPIRITS ARE HERE ILLEGALLY. So we
interrogate the door. WE INTERROGATE
WHAT HAPPENED AND WE BEGIN to deal with
them. AND SOME OF OUR FATHERS HAVE
ACTIVE ALTARS. They still consult
witches.
SOME OF THEM ARE EVEN WITCHES.
HALLELUJAH. So when you begin to DEAL
WITH AN ACTIVE ALTAR, you need to have
an ACTIVE LIFE.
THAT'S WHY OUR PRAYER FREQUENCIES ARE
NOT THE same because THE PATH OF OUR
DESTINY IS NOT THE SAME. I met one
preacher and he told me pastor you know
our sons and daughters need to meet. He
said imagine now if my son marries your
daughter you have dealt with
generational cases. You have dealt with
generational patterns. Imagine how much
they will prosper. And he said imagine a
a a stranger coming to your home with
generational altars and introduce that
pattern into your child. Say that's why
pastor's kids need to hang out around.
Say besides it's a GOOD THING SO THAT
OUR LABORS CAN ANSWER.
And so the second one we have is
freemasonry.
And freemasonry is very much
generational. By the way, many of the
masons recruit their children and it is
inherited.
And when you come from a family that has
Freemasons, you're coming from families
that have covenants with devils and
demons.
And that family you step out, you must
understand the covenant of the blood of
Jesus.
Please don't be deceived. Freemasons are
real. Don't be deceived. Uh it's nothing
about Satanism. That that's a lie. If
people are in a secret society and they
don't share their secrets, then why? How
can you believe what they tell you? And
they don't share their secrets. So these
rituals they're telling you, how do you
know it's true? So it takes intelligence
to know. And we have heard PEOPLE THAT
GOT BORN AGAIN. And they will tell you
rituals here are real. They are real.
You don't move from one degree to the
other without rituals. And it is so bad
that Freemasons can even sit in church
and you don't know.
THERE IS A RANK WHERE MEN CAN OPERATE
IN. UNLESS YOU ARE dealing with
discernment AND HIGHLEVEL INTENSIVE
WARFARE, you can eat with them. They can
even be the biggest givers in church
and MOST OF THE TIMES THEY TARGET THE
PASTOR AND THEY BEFRIEND THE PASTOR AND
THEY begin to give gifts to pastors and
THEY QUENCH HIS FIRE AND THEY NOW begin
to drain the altar.
AND THE CHURCH TURNS OUT TO BE A SOCIAL
CENTER. SO YOUR PASTOR IS WEARING
DESIGNER SUITS, DRIVING DESIGNER CARS,
PLAYING GOLF ON MONDAY, MEETING THE WHO
is who and he thinks that's anointing.
And what he does not know his anointing
WAS HIJACKED AND HIS ASSIGNMENT IN THAT
CITY WAS ABORTED. AND SO THE MEN ARE
RULING THAT TOWN BECAUSE THEY KNEW IF
YOU RISE OUR ALTARS ARE IN CHAOS.
That's why as a pastor not every gift
should be treated. That's why God must
deal with your greed and appetites
so that someone can come and give you 10
million and tell them sir I don't know
why but I don't feel like taking it.
Now, some of you are looking at me like,
"Hey, boss for Yes. Yes.
Yes. Because I know I know ministries
that were hijacked and I know ministries
where agents were sent and they got born
again. They could not withstand that
assignment." Hey, there's one in Akuru
where they were sent to attack the
ministry. After the assignment was
aborted, that church blew out.
It was in a place now where it was
growing. But today, it's now the
biggest. Why? They conquered that force.
And that church is founded on prayer. So
we know these people visit us, they
come, they see, they befriend the pastor
and then they begin to introduce social
ideas.
Imagine the church helping the poor.
Imagine the church building a hospital.
Imagine the church build they are not
bad. I have a vision of building one,
but that's not my core business.
I will not go to heaven with a hospital.
We will do them because we are dealing
with societies. But that cannot make me
lose sleep that I HAVE NO MONEY FOR
HOSPITAL. I will lose sleep when I have
no money for evangelism. I SAY LORD HOW
CAN THIS BE? THE CITY NEEDS JESUS. WE
NEED TO EVANGELIZE. SO THEY COME, they
come off ledge. They pray WITH YOU. THEY
BECOME elders in the boardroom. But they
they are very SCHEMING
to their rank they can weigh YOU AND
KNOW YOU ARE NOT A MAN OF PRAYER AND
KEEP YOU BUSY.
That's why any preacher and every
believer you must HAVE WHAT WE CALL
PERSONAL PRAYERS not corporate
DO
THAT level they cannot LOCATE YOU. AND
THAT'S WHEN NOW God begins to speak to
you and tells you pray in tones. As you
pray in tong, you begin to wage warfare.
And in that warfare, you don't know
you're breaking covenants. Meals you are
given, things you ate, they are now
losing their power over your life.
Yes.
Number three is Satanism.
Satanism.
Satanism is different from Freemasonry.
Satanism is where witchcraft is. This is
very much ritualistic.
This is where now people sacrifice
everything. Even men
uncertainist don't hide. THESE ARE EVIL
PUBLIC MEN. THEY DON'T HIDE. FREEMASONS
can come off like a people. Their main
idea is is control. That's their main
idea. But you can't control systems
without power. That's why the church
needs to rise. Hallelujah. The church
needs to rise because you can't control
systems without power.
Satanism is the one that is full of
rituals, sacrifices, witches, wizards,
sorcerers, all of them are under
Satanism.
This one now it's about invoking demonic
powers. And number four is occultism
because you're not dealing with a
prophet, you are dealing with a
sorcerer.
Desperation can push you there. Are we
together?
Covenant of salt.
covenant.
I KNOW DESPERATION CAN PUSH YOU. There's
one day
restoring stolen goods.
I won't LIE TO YOU. I WAS SO BITTER. I
was saying.
Yeah.
No, let's have a church. AND SOMETIMES
DESPERATION CAN PUSH you to go and seek
these services. Some of these men tie
you to their altars BECAUSE THE POWER
OPERATING IN THAT ALTAR is not of God.
They use familiar spirit. They use
intelligence of the marine kingdom. THEY
USE ALL MANNER OF POWERS.
THEY MIGHT TELL YOU SOMETHING THAT IS
true but the source is not of God. And
you WILL HEAR AND MOST OF THEM MOST OF
them some of these cults and orals most
of them they never read the new
testament they will never read the new
covenant THEY WILL ALWAYS TELL YOU EVEN
ABRAHAM RAISED AN altar
you also need to raise an altar and
that's why I need to come
a man raise an ALTAR ARE ALTARS about
money
AND IF YES WHAT ABOUT THOSE WHO HAVE NO
MONEY. IS THIS GOSPEL FOR THEM THAT CAN
AFFORD?
I'VE HEARD STORIES LIKE PASTOR, WE ARE
GOING THROUGH A FAMILY SHAKEUP AND I'VE
BEEN TOLD TO RAISE AN ALTAR AND SOME
PEOPLE EVEN GIVE AMOUNTS
150. And some of these people, let me
say the truth, they don't tithe. They
don't give. But in A MANIPULATIVE ALTAR,
YOU REALIZE THEY HAVE MONEY.
THEY ARE NOT FAITHFUL WITH THEIR WALK
WITH GOD,
but they want God to move now now. AND
THIS CONVERSATION IS VERY HIGH. AND I
KNOW PEOPLE making millions out of that
conversation.
AND I'VE ALSO HEARD TESTIMONIES.
Let's interrogate the matter.
There is something called
the law of counter.
THE LAW OF COUNTER. AND THAT LAW IS A
SPIRITUAL LAW.
The law of counter. AND THAT IS THE LAW
THAT WITCHES USE
THAT
SACRIFICE. So I need to look for a more
powerful witch to remove A MORE POWERFUL
SACRIFICE TO COUNTER YOUR SACRIFICE.
I HAVE HAD MEN TELL ME
we are not WITCHES
in this kingdom. I KNOW GOD HAS HAS
GIVEN MEN RANKS BUT WHEN IT COMES TO
MATTERS OF POWER THERE IS NO KIWANGO. IT
TAKES FAITH IN THE word of God.
HOW A BIGGER SACRIFICE. THAT'S WHY IT
OPERATES IN DARKNESS. You have a a
lesser witch who CAN DO SOMETHING. NOW
YOU NEED A GREATER WITCH.
SO A WITCH HIMSELF WILL tell you you
need someone OF A HIGHER. HE'S NOT in my
level SO I CAN'T UNDO HIS POWER. SO YOU
NEED SOMEONE OF A HIGHER POWER TO UNDO
HIS POWER. SOME WILL EVEN TELL YOU
BECAUSE LAND power
marine power. SO WE DON'T HAVE THE
FORMULA OF THE MARINE. WE HAVE THE
FORMULA OF THE DESERT LAND SPIRIT. SO WE
CAN'T UNDO. SO YOU NEED TO GO BACK to
Kisumu and look for people that are
operating in that system. I know I'm
talking. AND SO NOW BECAUSE OF OUR
AFRICAN MINDSET AND BECAUSE OF OUR
BACKGROUND OF WITCHCRAFT, WE HAVE NOT
YET BEEN DELIVERED. WE COME WITH THE
SAME MINDSET TO CHURCH. AND OUR QUESTION
IS HOW much
I've had those conversation
The Bible says the temple curtains were
torn into two so that you can enter and
I enter.
NO.
WHEN I CRY AND YOU CRY, ALL OF US ARE
HURT. THERE IS NO BADGE IN THE SPIRIT
THAT GOD HEARS SOME MEN AND IGNORES
OTHERS.
I know I'm just constructing some stuff
>> because I want you to have FAITH IN
JESUS, NOT IN A MAN.
>> OKAY? CAN GOD ANOINT ME? YES. CAN GOD
GIVE ME A RANK? YES. CAN GOD GIVE ME
AUTHORITY? YES. BUT HE CAN ALSO DO IT
UNTO YOU.
>> SO MY JOB IS NOT TO STAND IN ONE LEVEL
WHERE NO ONE ENTERS. I need to bring you
there
INSTEAD OF ME STAYING HERE SEVEN DAYS
PRAYING. I need to TELL YOU EVERY FIRST
WEEK WE ARE PRAYING. SO IF YOU DON'T
JOIN IN DURING THE MIDNIGHT PRAYER THEN
YOU HAVE FAILED BECAUSE THAT IS WHAT
KEEPS US IN THE FIRST WEEK WHEN WE ARE
FASTING AND YOU DON'T FAST THEN IT IS
NOT ME. YOU ARE DOING YOURSELF
UNJUSTICE. I AM WHOM I AM BECAUSE OF
THESE DISCIPLINES. SO IF YOU DON'T
FOLLOW ON THE DISCIPLINES THEN YOU HAVE
FAILED.
SO IF YOU WAIT FOR ME TO PRAY, YOU HAVE
TAKEN ME BACK IN THE DAYS OF MOSES WHERE
GO AND HEAR GOD. WE ARE HERE WITH AN
OFFERING ready to give you. Tell us what
he's saying. This day WE ARE GOING NOT.
WE ARE GOING. YOU HEAR GOD ABOUT YOUR
FAMILY. I HEAR GOD ABOUT MY FAMILY. YOU
HEAR GOD ABOUT YOUR BUSINESS, I HEAR GOD
ABOUT MY MINISTRY. WHEN WE GATHER HERE
ON SUNDAY, ALL OF US ARE GIVING THANKS.
AND SO NOW PEOPLE HAVE PUT US IN THAT
BOX of I need to raise an altar. LET ME
SAY THIS. GOD OPERATES SOMETIMES WITH
INSTRUCTIONS.
That pattern is very clear.
THE PROBLEM IS MY instruction may not be
your instruction.
ARE THERE PEOPLE THAT GOD commanded
to raise an offering and release it on
his altar and they got results? Yes.
But when we teach the Bible, we always
say your experiences are not doctrine.
Hello. Like I stand here on this
pullpit, I interrogated my family. I
realized there was a heavy hand of
poverty. heavy
and I began to pray this is the
instruction the Lord gave me.
So in my work for 10 years
that was the instruction allow me to
tell you I cannot tell you that if you
sense poverty you join me for 10 years
it may not work I have the grace I CAN
GO IN MY ACCOUNT GET 100,000 AND BRING
IT in church and feel happy you YOU WILL
COUNT 100,000 and cry and say mom ARE
YOU SERIOUS WHY YOU HAVE NO GRACE
I KNOW PEOPLE THAT WERE GOING THROUGH
BATTLES AND THE LORD SAYS LET'S meet in
the mountain for 21 days and a MAN
FASTED. I KNOW A MAN WHO WENT FOR 40
DAYS AND HE SAW A MAN IN THE SPIRIT AND
HE said to me
and IT WAS THE MAN CONTENDING FOR THE
FOR THE FOR THE DESTINY. AND AT THAT
TIME A PHONE CALL CAME THAT THEY HAD
FOUND THEIR title deed 10 acres that the
father left and they were struggling and
it was eaten AND THEY WERE IN POVERTY.
WHY? THERE WAS SOMETHING THAT WAS
HOLDING THEIR WEALTH AFTER 40 DAYS OF
PRAYER. NOW IF THAT MAN CAME TO TELL YOU
HOW THE LORD DELIVERED THEM OUT OF
POVERTY WILL TELL YOU 40 DAYS. I'LL TELL
you 10 years.
ANOTHER ONE WILL TELL YOU, I WENT TO A
MEETING AND I MET A MAN AND HE
PROPHESIED AND HE SAID I BREAK the cycle
and IT WAS BROKEN. NOW DOES THAT MEAN
THAT YOU NOW LOOK FOR PROPHETIC
MEETINGS? LISTEN, EVERYONE HAS UNIQUE
INSTRUCTIONS ACCORDING TO YOUR LEVEL AND
THERE ARE TESTIMONIES OF INSTRUCTIONS
THAT HAVE WORKED BUT THAT'S NOT THE ONLY
WAY OUT.
Am I speaking to anyone? SO THERE ARE
MEN HERE WHO CAN TELL YOU
and you know BECAUSE WE ARE NOT
THEOLOGIANS. WE USE DIFFERENT WORDS
MEANING DIFFERENT THINGS. SOMEONE WILL
TELL YOU
BUT IN THEIR hearts of HEARTS THEY KNOW
THEY WERE INSTRUCTED TO GIVE A GIVING.
But when I see it as a theologian I know
you can't raise an ALTAR BUT THE LORD
KNOWS WHAT YOU MEAN IN YOUR HEART.
HALLELUJAH. NOW I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU
BECAUSE THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO HAVE BUILT
MINISTRIES. YOU JUST TELL THEM YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH A FAMILY KILL. THEY'LL
TELL YOU ONE THING. You need to raise an
altar.
So 7 *
Jehovah. JEHOVAH
JEHOVAH
AND BECAUSE YOU ARE DESPERATE FOR REAL.
YOU CAN SEE pastor this is not where I
need to be. YOU GO AND LOOK FOR AN
ISAAC.
DO YOU KNOW GOD NEVER RECEIVED ISAAC?
NO. He was testing the heart. Said you
can keep the child. And do you know it
is THE LORD WHO TOLD ABRAHAM GO? Has the
Lord told you go? OR IS A MAN TELLING
YOU GO AND BRING ISAAC? PASTOR, ARE
THERE TIMES THAT GOD CAN ASK FOR AN
ISAAC? YES. And what is he doing? He's
circumcising you from Isaac SO THAT
ISAAC DOES NOT BECOME AN IDOL. SO THAT
YOU ARE THE BLESSING DON'T BECOME THE
BLESS YOU DON'T WORSHIP THE BLESSING.
YOU ARE SO MUCH TO THE BLESSER. THAT'S
THE REAL OF ISAAC THAT GOD CAN ASK YOU
in the PROPHET OF THIS MONTH BRING ALL
OF IT TO MY HOUSE SO THAT YOU DON'T
PROPHETS DON'T MOVE YOU. It is God that
moves you and he KNOWS YOU ARE PASSED
THE BEST. NOW YOUR HEART IS circumcised
and so there are men and this is the
worst part. You go to our fathers, you
go to elders that are in Kakama
Guandai, they will tell you the same
thing. You need to raise an altar. Now
it IS SAD WHEN A MAN GOES TO KYAMA AND
RAISES A SACRIFICE AND SEES RESULTS AND
HE WENT TO CHURCH RAISED AN ALTAR AND
THERE WAS NO RESULT. WHY WILL THEY COME
BACK TO CHURCH?
IF MONEY CAN DELIVER YOU THE poor have
failed then this Jesus came for the
rich.
I KNOW EVEN PEOPLE who take loans AND
THAT'S WHY THERE ARE MANY BITTER MEN IN
CHURCH. THEY THINK GOD HAS abandoned
them. THEY LOOK AND ASK, "PASTOR, WHAT
HAVE I NOT DONE?"
AND THE LORD IS SAYING, "YOU CAN'T RAISE
AN ALTAR. WHY? I RAISED ONE FOR YOU."
THERE IS NO OTHER ALTAR YOU CAN RAISE.
THERE IS NO OTHER ALTAR. YES, I KNOW
GIDEON RAISED AN ALTAR FOR ME, BUT I'M
THE ONE WHO TOLD HIM HOW TO DO IT. BUT
NOW ON CALVARY, I RAISED THE FINAL
ALTAR. ALL YOU NEED TO DO is pick this
ALTAR AND bring it to your home. Bring
Jesus TO YOUR HOME. WHY? THERE IS NO
OTHER ALTAR. EVEN IF YOU OFFER A 100
COWS, IT CAN NEVER MATCH THE ALTAR OF
CALVARY. WE NEED TO go back to the
cross. HALLELUJAH. THERE IS NO MAN,
THERE IS NO DEMAND IN THE OLD TESTAMENT
WHERE MEN WERE TOLD, "RAISE AN ALTAR
WITH YOUR OWN MONEY." THE LORD GAVE
INSTRUCTIONS. AND THE INSTRUCTIONS ENDED
AFTER CALVARY. THEY ENDED AFTER CALVARY
BECAUSE THAT ALTAR IS THE MOST LIFTED
ALTAR. THAT ALTAR HAS THE MOST PERFECT
SACRIFICE. THAT ALTAR HAS THE PERFECT
BLOOD. THAT ALTAR NEEDS FAITH. PASTOR,
WHAT DO I DO? THERE ARE GENERATIONAL
ALTARS IN MY FAMILY. YOU JUST NEED TO
KNOW THE POWER OF THE ALTAR OF JESUS. IF
YOU DON'T KNOW THE POWER OF THIS ALTAR,
YOU WILL THINK YOUR GRANDFATHER WHO
OPENED A DOOR BY WITCHCRAFT is more
powerful.
I met a preacher in Mombasa told me
I said that's the gospel. THAT'S THE
GOSPEL. GO BACK AND LISTEN TO WHAT our
parents used TO PREACH. THEY WILL GO TO
A CRUSADE AND TELL THEM
and they will TELL YOU WE LOST THAT
GOSPEL WHEN WE BEGAN TO INTRODUCE OUR
MANMADE PHILOSOPHY AND THAT'S WHY MEN
ARE NOT SEEING THE VICTORY OF CALVARY.
The church in Colossians and that's the
church in Kenya now they did not have a
problem believing Jesus but they had a
problem believing in Jesus in totality
that's the problem the church TODAY THEY
HAVE NO PROBLEM believing that Jesus can
save but they feel Jesus cannot deliver
me from generational altars this one I
MUST FIX MYSELF THAT IS OUR ERROR WE
HAVE NO PROBLEM BELIEVING THAT JESUS CAN
WASH ME WITH HIS BLOOD BUT WE STILL
believe I need to give HIM A 100,000 TO
BREAK the altar that existed in my
FATHER'S HOUSE. AND PAUL WRITES TO THAT
church and tells them because they were
struggling. They were born again, BUT
THEY STILL FELT WE need to be
circumcised. THEY THEY STILL THEY WERE
CAUGHT UP IN MYSTICISM. And Paul tells
them Christ is the sovereign authority.
He's the creator of all. THERE IS
NOTHING THAT STANDS WITHOUT HIM. HE'S
THE ONE THAT HOLDS THE UNIVERSE IN HIS
HAND. I CAME TO TELL THE CHURCH, CHRIST
IS THE HOLDER OF ALL. THERE IS NO ALTAR
THAT IS POWERFUL THAN JESUS. THERE IS NO
CAST, NO POWER THAT IS POWERFUL THAN THE
POWER OF CALVARY. WE NEED TO BELIEVE
THAT CHRIST GAVE US THE MOST POWERFUL
ALTAR. PASTOR, WHAT DO I DO WHEN I KNOW
THERE IS AN ALTAR? ENTER WHERE Peter
entered. HE WAS TOLD, I WILL GIVE YOU
THE KEYS of the KINGDOM OF ZION.
WHATEVER YOU SHOUT IS SHUT. YOU NEED TO
WAKE UP KNOWING ALL POWER AND AUTHORITY
HAS BEEN GIVEN TO ME AND NOW I SEND YOU
THEE. IF YOU BELIEVE in my name, YOU
SHALL CAST OUT DEVILS. IF YOU BELIEVE IN
MY NAME, YOU SHALL STEP ON SERPENTS AND
SCORPIONS. IF YOU BELIEVE IN MY NAME,
YOU SHALL SPEAK IN A NEW TONGUE. YOU
NEED TO ENTER IN YOUR OWN HOME DURING
THIS DECEMBER HOLIDAY. I'M SAYING IN THE
NAME OF JESUS, I COME AS A PRIEST OF
YAHWEH. I COME TO PLANT THE ALTAR OF
JESUS IN THIS HOUSE. ANY OTHER ALTAR
THAT SPEAKS HERE, I SILENCE IT NOW. I
DECLARE THE SPIRIT OF THE BLOOD. I
DECLARE THE ALTAR OF JEHOVAH SHALL WALK
OUT HERE. I DESTROY THE ALTARS OF MY
GRANDFATHER, ALTARS OF MY PARENTS, ANY
ALTAR THAT RULETH IN THIS HOUSE, I COME
FOR IT RIGHT NOW. MAY THE LORD ARISE
THAT HIS ENEMIES MAY BE SCATTERED. WE
NEVER CAME TO A DEFEATED KINGDOM. WE
CAME TO A POWERFUL KINGDOM. YOU DON'T
NEED TO RAISE AN ALTAR. THERE IS AN
ALTAR RAISED FOR YOU. THE ALTAR OF
CALVARY, IT HAS THE BEST SACRIFICE. ANY
DOOR THAT WAS OPENED, YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO CLOSE IT. SOME OF US, WE NEED TO
STAND. PETER SAID, JESUS SAID, BECAUSE
YOU KNOW WHO I AM, WHO AM I? YOU ARE
JESUS THE CHRIST. HE SAID, THE
REVELATION OF WHO I AM, THAT REVELATION
IS ALL YOU NEED. is God, THE CREATOR OF
ALL, THE ANCIENT OF DAYS, THE ONE THAT
WAS, THE ONE THAT IS AND THE SOONCOMING
KING, THE ONE THAT HOLDS THE PAST AND
HOLDS THE FUTURE, THE ONE THAT CAN
JOURNEY IN MY YESTERDAY AND UNDO
WHATEVER WAS DONE. HE IS GOD BY HIMSELF.
HE IS AFRAID. HE'S THE CREATOR OF
EVERYTHING. WHEN YOU UNDERSTAND WHO HE
IS, THE ONE THAT DIED AND ROSE BACK ON
THE THIRD DAY, WHEN YOU KNOW WHO HE IS,
HE SAID UPON THIS ROCK, UPON THIS
REVELATION, I WILL BUILD MY CHURCH AND
THE GATES OF HELL CANNOT PREVAIL. THE
GATES OF HELL CANNOT PREVAIL. I CAME TO
DECLARE THAT IS THE WORD OF GOD. HE HAS
EXALTED HIS WORD ABOVE HIS TITLES. THE
GATES OF HELL CANNOT PREVAIL OVER YOUR
FAMILY. YOU DON'T NEED 150. YOU DON'T
NEED ANOTHER GOD. YOU DON'T NEED ANOTHER
COW. WE CANNOT BE REDEEMED BY THE BLOOD
OF BULLS. WE ARE DELIVERED BY THE BLOOD
OF ELONOR. WE ARE SANCTIFIED IN THIS
SERVICE. I DECLARE LET THE BLOOD SPEAK
IN YOUR FAMILY. LET THE BLOOD OF YESHUA,
LET THE SOUND OF THE BLOOD NOW ARISE TO
UNDO ANY OTHER BLOOD THAT SPEAKS THERE.
WE DECLARE IN THIS HOUR ANY LEAK OR
DEMON THAT OPERATES IN MY FAMILY, DEMONS
OF OPPRESSION, DEMONS OF AFFLICTION,
DEMONS OF ATTACK, WHATEVER DOOR THAT WAS
OPEN, I TAKE AUTHORITY NOW. I TAKE
AUTHORITY NOW. AS A CHILD OF GOD, I TAKE
AUTHORITY. AS A PRIEST OF ZION, I TAKE
AUTHORITY. I SHUT EVERY DOOR.
I SHOUT EVERY DOOR THOSE OF POVERTY,
WITCHCRAFT, SORCERY, FREEMASONRY,
SATANISM ORISM. YOU CANNOT PREVAIL. YOU
CANNOT PREVAIL. YOU cannot prevail.
WE IDENTIFY WITH THE COMPLETE WORK OF
CALVARY. WE IDENTIFY WITH THE FINAL
SACRIFICE. WE IDENTIFY WITH THE DEALINGS
OF THE CROSS. WE IDENTIFY WITH THE BLOOD
OF THE LAMB. WE IDENTIFY WITH THE
DEALINGS THE COMPLETE WORK OF CALVARY.
LET THE ALTAR OF JESUS LET IT SPEAK IN
MY FAMILY. LET THE ALTAR of Jesus SPEAK
IN MY FAMILY. I COME AS A KID. I COME TO
PLANT THE ALTAR OF THE LORD. I BRING
DOWN THE ALTARS OF POWER. ALTARS OF
SORCERY. I BRING DOWN GODS OF MY
FATHER'S GODS IN MY FATHER'S HOUSE. YOU
CANNOT SPEAK. I STAND AS A PRIEST.
WE CANNOT SUFFER. WHATEVER OUR PARENTS
SUFFER, WE CANNOT SUFFER. WHATEVER THE
GENERATION, WE ARE ACCEPTED. WE ARE
ACCEPTED.
THE AUTHORITY OF CHRIST. THE AUTHORITY
OF CHRIST IN MY HOME.
YES, LORD.
LISTEN, THE BIBLE SAYS WE ARE A
GENERATION OF PRIESTS AND KINGS. YOU
HAVE THE POWER TO PLANT THE ALTAR OF
YOUR WAY. THE GIDEON ANOINTING IS UPON
YOU. YOU SHALL BRING DOWN AND ERECT THE
ALTAR AS A PRIEST ORDINATION UPON YOUR
LIFE. YOU HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO SAY IN
THIS HOUSE, I PLANT THE ALTAR OF
CALVARY. LET THE BLOOD OF JESUS SPEAK IN
MY FAMILY. ANY OTHER BLOOD THAT IS
CONTRARY TO THIS FAMILY, WE CANCEL THAT
BLOOD. YOU HAVE THE POWER TO BRING THE
ALTAR OF YESHUA INTO YOUR HOUSEHOLD.
Oh Jesus, WE NEVER GOT BORN AGAIN TO
SUFFER. WE ARE THE deliverers of our
homes. We are the deliverers of our
homes. PEOPLE WILL RECEIVE DIFFERENT
INSTRUCTIONS, BUT THE FINAL SOLUTION IS
THE CROSS OF CALVARY. I SAY THE FINAL
SOLUTION IS THE CROSS OF CALVARY. I
STAND ON THIS ALTAR AND I WANT TO
declare any LEGAL DEMON THAT OPERATED IN
YOUR LIFE WITHOUT YOUR KNOWLEDGE BY THE
VERDICT OF THIS REVELATION, WE COMMAND
THEM TO LEAVE OUR LIVES, LEAVE OUR
FAMILIES, LEAVE OUR HOMES, ANY DOOR THAT
WAS OPEN. ANY DEMON THAT STANDS LEGALLY
IN MY FAMILY, I DECLARE NOW AS A PRIEST
OF THAT HOUSE, AS A PRIEST OF THAT HOME,
I COMMAND YOU TO LEAVE. I COMMAND YOU TO
LEAVE. I COMMAND YOU TO LEAVE. I COMMAND
YOU TO LEAVE. BEGIN TO ENGAGE RIGHT NOW.
ANYTHING THAT OPPRESSED YOUR LIFE,
OPPRESSED YOUR FAMILY,
command them to leave.
THEY CANNOT FUNCTION.
LISTEN,
PASTOR, is it possible for a man to be
born again and be oppressed? Yes.
I was born again and I was facing
oppression,
demons.
No. They say in the jungle
when a man is afraid
there is an there is a scent that you
release.
That's why when you are walking in the
jungle even dogs can sense. That's why
there are people who pass in a place and
dogs begin to bark and they run and they
chase them because the fear releases
some hormones and they dispel some
scent. But when a man is bold, a dog
will look at you and not even touch you.
THAT'S HOW HAVE YOU EVER WONDERED HOW
THE MASAI children they pass through the
MARA AND THEY GO TO SCHOOL PASSING
ELEPHANTS and they don't touch them
because elephants can PICK A SCENT.
MESSAI MEET WITH LIONS AND lions flee.
They can't attack them because there is
a nature of boldness. They have been
raised in that jungle and they know that
they are here legally and they know this
is our home and we can't leave. Is
either the lion leaves but we can't
leave. Listen, you need to know you are
here legally. YOU NEED TO KNOW YOU ARE
NOT THE ONE TO LEAVE.
And for it is possible for demons to
take advantage. I was born again and
preaching the gospel, but I was still
asking my mom for money. Married, but I
could not even move my family until I
realized there is error. The first level
of deliverance is knowing the truth.
There is a confidence that come when men
know the truth. Demons can oppress but
when a man knows the truth, the
oppression comes to an end. So we are
not dealing with men that have been
possessed. We are dealing with ignorance
that attracted oppression. So there are
things happening in your life and you
have been praying prayers thinking maybe
is it that a sacrifice I never raised.
Here's something I want to tell you. It
is not in your money. It's not in your
money. It is in your faith in the
complete work of Calvary.
That's it. That's it.
I have never raised an altar, but I
brought the altar of your way in my
home. I said, Jesus, you must live here.
The blood must speak here.
>> These dealings must work here.
And I discovered if you open that path
of 100,000 50,000 150 then why did Jesus
die on the cross? All you needed was to
work hard, get money, deliver yourself.
There must be something greater than
your money. And that is the power of
Zion.
>> And that's why when that deliverance
comes, your faith will never be in your
money. Your faith will be in him that
delivers. He said upon this rock, what
was that rock? Peter, who am I? Who do
men say that I am? You are the Christ,
the son of the living God. He says, that
revelation is enough to build a
foundation where no demonic dog can
operate.
The Lord has been putting it in my heart
and he has been telling me, son, begin
to teach men me. Teach them me because
I'm the only one who can fix them.
People know so much, but they don't know
me. When they begin to know me, matters
will begin to come down. We are not the
ones to retreat. There is a place you
reach, you don't even retreat. You are
the one who begins to attack. You enter
in the house of your auntie who is a
witch and you stay there and you say, I
come as a priest of Zion and I come to
rule out any altar of Bal in this family
and I serve notice. Some of us we need
to go to barriers. When you are given
time to speak that theology, you say,
"We know these are not natural deaths."
But I'm here to send a warning. Anyone
that is in church, mercy or judgment,
next barrier. If you don't repent who
will bury you and you walk out of that
wedding, they might look at you. They
they met pastor Peter. Pastor Peter went
to a meeting and there were these
elders. He said, "In this wedding, we
are not going the traditional way." They
said, "You can't insult the gods." He
said, "No, we are going the bibilical
way." They said, "You don't know us." He
got an accident. That day they attacked
him. He got an accident. I told him sir
go and tell them if they do not repent
who will bury them. One of those men
said it's only pastor D who can pray for
me. You are a young boy. We we we we are
not here to retreat and negotiate. A
time has come where the power of our God
must be seen. There are people you need
to look straight in the eye and tell
them sir enough is enough. Is either you
die or you repent. And I've given you
one year. Either you die or repent. I
know those levels because we were tied
in our family. I told my wife we make
these prayers. She say either Barry or
mercy. She said I asked are you ready?
She said uh I told her the day you are
ready tell me. She said now I'm ready.
We made that prayer. Mercy never showed
up. Because the person was not willing
to repent. People had died in family.
Someone died. The the key person died.
The power you know when a when a
transformer is interrupted power
networks interrupted. It takes another
50, 100 years for another transformer to
arise. Before that transformer arises,
you introduce the transformer of Jehovah
AND THE POWER OF God begins to go. We
know there are men IN OUR HOMES WHO HAVE
STOOD AS PRINCIPALITIES. We know there
are people that TRANSACT WITH OUR STARS.
THEY COME AND DEAL WITH OUR CHILDREN.
YOU THINK THEY'RE COMING TO SAY HI TO
YOUR CHILD, BUT THEY ARE THERE TO
INTERROGATE THEIR DESTINY AND TAMPER
WITH OUR STARS. WE ARE HERE TO SERVE
THEM. NOTICE WE ARE STANDING ON THE MOST
POWERFUL ALTAR, THE ALTAR OF CALVARY. WE
ARE STANDING WHERE THE BIBLE SAYS HE WAS
PUBLICLY BESOUND ON THAT ALTAR. AND WE
ARE HERE TO DECLARE IT IS EITHER MERCY
OR JUDGMENT. IF THEY DON'T REPENT, LET
THE SWORD OF JUDGMENT LOCATE THEIR
HOUSES. IT IS TIME FOR ANYTHING THAT
STANDS ON THE PATHWAY OF YOUR DESTINY.
IT IS EITHER THEY COME UNDER THE BLOOD
OR THEY ARE TAKEN OUT. I DECLARE FROM
THIS HOUR NO MORE OPPRESSION OVER YOUR
LIFE. WHATEVER THAT WAS TIED, LET THE
LORD OPEN IT UP. WHATEVER THAT WAS HELD,
LET IT BE RELEASED RIGHT NOW. ANY
CONTENTION IN THE SPIRIT, LET IT END AT
THIS HOUR IN THE MIGHTY NAME OF JESUS. I
UNTIE YOU FROM ANY ALTAR THAT CALL THE
NAME OF YOUR FAMILY. I UNTIE YOUR
CHILDREN. I UNTIE YOUR DESTINY. I UNTIE
EVERYTHING THAT HAS CONNECTED YOU TO
THAT ALTAR. AND TODAY I DECLARE BY THE
VERDICT OF REDEMPTION, BY THE VERDICT OF
SALVATION, I CONNECT YOU TO THE ALTARS
OF CALVARY, LET THE BLOOD SPEAK OVER
YOUR LIFE. LET THE BLOOD SPEAK OVER YOUR
LIFE. LET THE COMPLETE WORK OF CALVARY
BEGIN TO SHAPE YOUR DESTINY. LET THE
RESURRECTION POWER DEAL WITH ANY POWER
THAT IS CONTRARY TO YOUR LIFE. I CLEAR
THE WAY FOR YOU. I DECLARE ACCELERATION.
I DECLARE SUPERNATURAL UPLIFT. WHATEVER
WAS STOLEN, I COMMAND IT TO BE RESTORED.
EVERY BATTLE OF INHERITANCE, LET IT BE
RESTORED AT THIS HOUR. WHATEVER THEY
TOOK AWAY. THE HEALTH OF OUR CHILDREN,
THE DESTINIES OF OUR FAMILY, WHATEVER
THAT HAS BEEN HIDDEN IN GRAVES, WHATEVER
THAT WAS BURIED, WE UNBARRIED RIGHT NOW.
WE UNARRIED RIGHT NOW. WHEREVER THEY
BURIED OUR MONEY, BURIED OUR STUFF,
BURIED OUR RESOURCES, BURIED OUR WEALTH
TODAY IN THE NAME OF JESUS. IN THE NAME
OF JESUS. IN THE NAME OF JESUS. WE UNURY
THEM NOW. WE DECLARE NOW. LET THE FIRE
OF JUDGMENT FALL ON THE ALTAR. WE
RELEASE THE FIRE. THE FIRE OF GOD.
LET THE FIRE FALL ON THE ALTAR. LET THE
FIRE FALL ON THE ALTAR. THEM THAT
MENTION US. ON THE ALTARS OF THE WICKED,
LET FIRE FALL ON THAT ALTAR. THEM THAT
ARE THERE TO TAKE US OUT. TAKE OUR
BUSINESS, TAKE OUR FAMILIES, ALTARS OF
SATIS, ALTARS OF RELATIONS, ALTARS OF
CULTIVARS
THAT ARE AGAINST OUR LIVES. WE DECLARE
FIRE. LET THE JUDGMENT FIRE BE RELEASED
UPON THOSE ALTARS.
I SENSE DELIVERANCE.
I SENSE DELIVERANCE. DESTINIES ARE BEING
UNTIED.
EVERY VIOLENT WOMB WE COMMAND IT TO
OPEN. WHEREVER THEY T YOUR WOMB, OPEN
UP. OPEN UP. OPEN UP. CHILDREN ARE
COMING. THE FRUIT OF THE WOMB IS COMING.
WHEREVER THEY T YOUR MONEY,
WHEREVER THEY T YOUR WORLD, WE ARE.
Oh Jesus.
I see a lot of belie in the spirit.
And this word is very loud. Inheritance.
Inheritance. Inheritance. Inheritance.
Inheritance.
Hallelujah. Every battle of inheritance.
And we set you on the battle of
prosperity.
May you prosper in a kingdom. May you
prosper in a kingdom.
Jesus.
LISTEN. WHERE YOU CANNOT REACH, the fire
will reach.
We serve the ANCIENT OF DAYS. WHERE YOU
CANNOT ENTER, THE HOLY Ghost cannot be
hindered. There is an undoing in the
spirit.
There is an undoing.
Some of us are meant to be the lifters
of our families, but things are not
working out.
May you enter a place of no contention.
>> A place of no contention.
>> There is a place you enter and there are
no war. You know that you have conquered
and broken a few things. May you enter
that level.
>> Ah and in your own home where you are
plant the altar of Jesus.
I know people will say we need a family
altar. A family altar is simply a place
you gather to lift Jesus, to exalt him,
to worship him. That's the only thing
you can do. That's the only family altar
that we can raise. Please don't be
deceived. And if there be anyone here
who released money in an occultic
prophetic altar in the name of
deliverance and that money has been
speaking, we say, "I bless that voice."
>> The Bible says, "In the days of
ignorance, I the Lord overlooked." There
there are men that claim us because we
connected to their altar and they feel
entitled that you can't succeed without
them and it is a spiritual law but we
are rising upon that law and we are
saying your name cannot be claimed on
any altar where desperation pushed you
today we are pushing you out
>> in the name of Jesus
>> and anyone that mentions your name
>> on any altar from this hour
>> people that are jealous, malicious,
>> that go with rituals.
>> Oh Jesus,
>> we announce
may the terror of God show up
>> and the judgments of God show up.
>> A lady tried to take me to a witch. She
took my photo and she was told leave
this man alone. It is called the terror
of God. The Bible says when Jacob was
going to meet Esau, the terror of God
went ahead of him. Today the terror of
God will go ahead of you
>> that no man can mention your name on any
evil altar and nothing connected to your
life can be hijacked. Hallelujah in the
name of Jesus.